IGWE-DONUWE FAVOUR NNEOMA

FRONT DESK/CUSTOMER SERVICE

1 Brethren street, Powerline, Jakande, Ojo, Lagos Phone: +2348185113380 Email: moifaig@gmail.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Dedicated, resourceful and friendly professional with 2 years experience in business development and creating long lasting relationship with clients. I am an active person with the ability to identify customers' needs/problems, proffer reliable solutions and carry out tasks with intelligence and efficiency. I have conducted several field marketing activities and handled customers' accounts efficiently.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Whitehorse Group Limited 88, Lagos-Abeokuta Expressway, Dopemu, Lagos. Business Development / Administrative Officer November 2020 – April 2021

Responsibilities

- Carried out active and field marketing strategies to generate new customers.
- Listened and responded to customers' needs and concerns.
- Drafted and responded to letters of interests/business proposals.
- Monitored incoming and outgoing visitors.
- Oversaw incoming and outgoing mails.
- Oversaw daily activities in the organization.

Beloxxi Industries Limited 8A Kudirat Abiola Way, Oregun Ikeja, Lagos State Marketing / Customer Care Executive July 2019 – September 2020

Responsibilities

- Carried out active and field marketing strategies to generate new customers.
- Listened and responded to customers' needs and concerns.
- Managed distributors in a region with a team.
- Carried out successful sales activities in various markets.
- Carried out activations of new products in schools.

Success World International Limited Alaba International Market Ojo, Alaba, Lagos state Sales Executive April 2019- July 2019

Responsibilities

- · Generated new customers through marketing.
- Received and properly recorded customers' orders for transactions.
- Maintained customers through active customer care services.

National Youth Service Corps (NYSC) Program Girls High School Ugwuoba, Enugu State Teacher 2017 – 2018

Responsibilities

- Taught Literature in English for Senior Secondary School One (SSS1)
- Conducted and Invigilated examinations
- Counselled students on decisions concerning education and careers
- Served as house leader and records keeper for Inter house sports activities

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts (second class Upper) Linguistics

University of Uyo - 2017

French Module 1 Certificate

Nigerian French Language Village - 2011

Senior School Leaving Certificate

Great Alpha Comprehensive College - 2010

SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- Web Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Office, Data Processing.
- Excellent documentation skill and ability to multitask.
- Communication skills, great team spirit, customer service skills.
- Quick to learn and comprehend concepts.
- Ability to work under little or no supervision and/or pressure.
- Excellent command of English language.

TRAINING & CERTIFICATION

National Youth Service Corps (NYSC) 2017 Certificate of National Service

Skill Acquisition and Entrepreneurship Development Training (SAED) 2017 Certificate of Participation

INTERESTS

Reading, Writing, Research, Networking, Travelling

CORE VALUES

Honesty, Team Spirit, Accountability, Dedication, Passion and Efficiency

REFEREES

Available on request.